{"classes":["ORG","GPE","PERSON","LOC"],"annotations":[["\"The Website Socialization Activity in Nanggroe Aceh Darussalam was held today, June 19, where the Website Socialization event was opened by the Regional Head of the Department of Religion, Prop. NAD in this case is represented by the Head of Subdivision.\"\r",{"entities":[[39,63,"GPE"]]}],["\"Apart from plantation commodities, North Sumatra is also known as a producer of horticultural commodities (vegetables and fruit); for example Medan Oranges, Deli Guava, Cabbage, Tomatoes, Potatoes and Carrots.\"\r",{"entities":[[36,49,"GPE"]]}],["The potential of natural resources and the strategic position of the region make South Sumatra Province one of the regions whose economy is growing rapidly.\r",{"entities":[[81,103,"GPE"]]}],["\"West Sumatra Province, with its geographical conditions, is in the ring of fire, so it is very vulnerable to megathrusts which cause West Sumatra to have a very high frequency of disasters.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,22,"GPE"]]}],["Police arrested a housewife with the initials Y for allegedly selling her biological child to a philanderer in Bengkulu.\r",{"entities":[[111,119,"GPE"]]}],["Deputy Chairman of Commission II DPR RI Junimart Girsang highlighted that the issuance of a number of land certificates in Riau Province is still hampered by overlapping land with forest areas.\r",{"entities":[[40,56,"PERSON"],[123,136,"GPE"]]}],["The Indonesian government took over control of the Flight Information Region (FIR) or air space services for the Riau and Natuna Islands region after 78 years of being controlled by Singapore.\r",{"entities":[[113,117,"GPE"],[122,136,"GPE"],[182,191,"GPE"]]}],["\"A robber squandered the stolen money worth IDR 250 million to avoid being chased by residents in Maro Sebo District, Jambi.\"\r",{"entities":[[98,116,"LOC"],[118,123,"GPE"]]}],["The Prabowo Subianto-Gibran Rakabuming Raka pair was officially appointed President-Vice President for the 2024-2029 period by the Indonesian KPU. Frame craftsmen in Bandar Lampung started selling photos of this couple.\r",{"entities":[[166,180,"GPE"]]}],["\"The Bangka Belitung Islands Provincial Health Service asked the public, especially parents, to be aware of the transmission of the Singapore flu virus to children after the Idul Fitri 1445 Hijri holiday.\"\r",{"entities":[[5,28,"GPE"]]}],["\"A mother named Natalia (32) in Sanggau Regency, West Kalimantan experienced the unfortunate fate of being attacked by a crocodile and her right leg was severed. The victim was attacked by a crocodile while bathing in the Kapuas River.\"\r",{"entities":[[16,23,"PERSON"],[32,47,"GPE"],[49,64,"GPE"],[222,234,"LOC"]]}],["\"National level Musabaqah Tilawatil Qur'an (MTQ) will be held in Samarinda City, East Kalimantan (Kaltim) in September 2024.\"\r",{"entities":[[65,79,"GPE"],[81,96,"GPE"],[98,104,"GPE"]]}],["\"The Banjarmasin City Government, South Kalimantan received the 2024 best regional development award at the provincial level from the local provincial government.\"\r",{"entities":[[34,50,"GPE"]]}],["\"The HIV/AIDS Control Commission (KPA), Central Kalimantan Province (Kalteng) recorded cases of the spread of this virus that attacks the body's immune system reaching 2,400 cases according to December 2023 data.\"\r",{"entities":[[40,67,"GPE"],[69,76,"GPE"]]}],["\"A young man with the initials MN (20) in Tarakan, North Kalimantan (Kaltara) was determined to steal from a girls' boarding house and threatened the victim using a sharp weapon (sajam).\"\r",{"entities":[[42,49,"GPE"],[51,67,"GPE"],[69,76,"GPE"]]}],["\"The rubbish that polluted Teluk Beach, Teluk Village, Labuan District, Pandeglang Regency, Banten, was removed by the government and local community. The piled up rubbish was dumped at the landfill in Bojong Canar.\"\r",{"entities":[[27,38,"LOC"],[40,53,"LOC"],[55,70,"LOC"],[72,90,"GPE"],[92,98,"GPE"],[202,214,"LOC"]]}],["\"The Ministry of Environment and Forestry (KLHK) explained that one of the main contributors to air pollution in DKI Jakarta is the transportation sector, reaching 44 percent.\"\r",{"entities":[[113,124,"GPE"]]}],["\"The province of�West Java�continues to be determined to reduce the number of�stunting. Currently, the stunting rate in this region still reaches 20.2% or greater than the central government's target of 14% by 2024.\"\r",{"entities":[[14,36,"GPE"]]}],["\"The Meteorology, Climatology and Geophysics Agency (BMKG)�urges the people of�Central Java�(Central Java) to remain alert to the potential for hydrometeorological disasters such as floods and landslides even though there is currently a transition period from the rainy season to the dry season.\"\r",{"entities":[[76,92,"GPE"],[93,105,"GPE"]]}],["The transmigration quota for the Special Region of Yogyakarta (DIY) experiences a decreasing trend every year.\r",{"entities":[[33,61,"GPE"],[63,66,"GPE"]]}],["\"The mother-in-law in Probolinggo, East Java reported her son-in-law to the police. That was because the son-in-law was suddenly hit with wood by his father-in-law.\"\r",{"entities":[[22,33,"GPE"],[35,44,"GPE"]]}],["Minister of Tourism and Creative Economy (Menparekraf) Sandiaga Salahuddin Uno stated that tourist arrivals on the island of Bali are piling up in the southern part of Bali.\r",{"entities":[[55,78,"PERSON"],[125,129,"GPE"],[151,172,"LOC"]]}],["\"The years of dedication of 249 health workers in Manggarai, East Nusa Tenggara, turned out to have bitter results. Apart from being paid little and wages being paid late, now they are losing their jobs just because they claim their rights.\"\r",{"entities":[[50,59,"GPE"],[61,79,"GPE"]]}],["\"West Nusa Tenggara Province officially joined membership in the Construction Sector Transparency Initiative (CoST), a global infrastructure transparency initiative in Mataram.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,28,"GPE"],[168,175,"GPE"]]}],["\"An earthquake measuring magnitude (M) 5.3 rocked Boalemo Regency, Gorontalo Province. The depth of the earthquake was 156 km.\"\r",{"entities":[[50,65,"GPE"],[67,86,"GPE"]]}],["\"A Brimob member with the initials Bharaka SB was found hanging dead in his house in Central Mamuju Regency (Mateng), West Sulawesi (Sulbar). Police said the victim had a history of mental illness.\"\r",{"entities":[[85,107,"GPE"],[109,115,"GPE"],[118,131,"GPE"],[133,139,"GPE"]]}],["\"Five men in Banggai Regency, Central Sulawesi (Sulteng) ganged up on a TNI member named Panji Saputra. The perpetrators had previously abused the victim's younger brother in a different location.\"\r",{"entities":[[13,28,"GPE"],[30,46,"GPE"],[48,55,"GPE"],[89,103,"PERSON"]]}],["\"A man with the initials RB (22) in Manado City, North Sulawesi (Sulut), was found hanging dead in the room of his brother's house. Police found an apology letter written by the victim to his family.\"\r",{"entities":[[36,47,"GPE"],[49,63,"GPE"],[65,70,"GPE"]]}],["\"Two motorbike theft specialists with the initials A (19) and S (19) in Kendari, Southeast Sulawesi (Sultra) were arrested by the police. The mode of action of the two perpetrators was to act according to the orders of their gang boss.\"\r",{"entities":[[72,79,"GPE"],[81,99,"GPE"],[101,107,"GPE"]]}],["\"Earth Day is celebrated every April 22, carried out by various components of society in South Sulawesi (Sulsel), from activists, nature lovers, to local governments.\"\r",{"entities":[[89,103,"GPE"],[105,111,"GPE"]]}],["\"A print media journalist named Fadli Kayoa (25) in Ternate City, North Maluku (Malut) was hit by the driver of the North Maluku Golkar Party DPD I Secretary Arifin Djafar named Rio.\"\r",{"entities":[[32,43,"PERSON"],[52,64,"GPE"],[66,78,"GPE"],[80,85,"GPE"],[158,171,"PERSON"],[178,181,"PERSON"]]}],["\"An earthquake measuring magnitude (M) 4.7 rocked West Seram Regency, Maluku. The epicenter of the earthquake was 10 kilometers (Km) deep.\"\r",{"entities":[[50,68,"GPE"],[70,77,"GPE"]]}],["Commander of Military Resort Command 121/Alambhana Wanawai Brigadier General TNI Luqman Arief said soldiers from Infantry Battalion 642/Kapuas were ready to depart for West Papua for border security operations in the local area.\r",{"entities":[[81,93,"PERSON"],[168,178,"GPE"]]}],["\"TNI Commander General Agus Subiyanto, Maruli continued, asked the army not to hesitate to take action against OPM who were posing as Papuans. Moreover, if they carry weapons.\"\r",{"entities":[[23,37,"PERSON"]]}],["\"The Center for Meteorology, Climatology and Geophysics (BBMKG) Region V Jayapura, issued a weather forecast for all districts in Central Papua.\"\r",{"entities":[[73,81,"GPE"],[130,143,"GPE"]]}],["\"The head of Modusit Village in the Bintang Mountains Regency, Papua Mountains, named Timo Kasipmabin (45), was shot dead by members of the armed criminal group (KKB) led by Ananis Ataa Mimin.\"\r",{"entities":[[36,61,"GPE"],[63,78,"GPE"],[86,101,"PERSON"],[174,191,"PERSON"]]}],["\"PDI Perjuangan received the highest number of votes for the 2024 DPR RI Legislative Election (Pileg) in the South Papua electoral district. PDIP won 54,416 votes.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,15,"ORG"],[109,120,"GPE"]]}],["\"Member of the Free Papua Organization (OPM) Karel Fatem was sentenced to life imprisonment in the case of the attack on Yon Zipur 20/PPA soldiers who were repairing a bridge in Maybrat, Southwest Papua. The tragedy caused Serda Miskel Rumbiak to die and 4 other soldiers were injured.\"\r",{"entities":[[45,56,"PERSON"],[178,185,"GPE"],[187,203,"GPE"],[223,243,"PERSON"]]}],["\"Due to the lack of awareness of visitors in protecting the environment, Lhok Bubon Village Beach, West Aceh, was full of rubbish after the Eid holiday.\"\r",{"entities":[[73,97,"LOC"],[99,108,"GPE"]]}],["A detainee in a case of abuse in Southwest Aceh (Abdya) with the initials H (57) escaped while being treated at the hospital (RS). The police admitted that H ran away due to the negligence of the police officers on guard.\r",{"entities":[[33,47,"GPE"],[49,54,"GPE"]]}],["Mahdi said that a resident of Aceh Besar Regency was known to have become a victim of fraud after being caught in a fraud method that used social media and WhatsApp in his name.\r",{"entities":[[0,5,"PERSON"],[30,48,"GPE"]]}],["The High Prosecutor's Office (Kejati) conveyed developments in the handling of investigations into cases of alleged corruption involving irregularities in aid from the People's Palm Oil Rejuvenation Program (PSR) in Aceh Jaya Regency.\r",{"entities":[[216,233,"GPE"]]}],["A tectonic earthquake measuring Magnitude (M) 3.7 rocked South Aceh Regency on Monday 23 October 2023 at 04.51 WIB. The earthquake was triggered by plate subduction.\r",{"entities":[[57,75,"GPE"]]}],["The color of the decoration is predominantly silver in accordance with the age of the�Aceh�Singkil�Regency which has entered 25 years or its silver anniversary.\r",{"entities":[[82,106,"GPE"]]}],["Residents in Aceh Tamiang were shocked by the discovery of a woman's body covered in palm oil leaf fronds in an oil palm plantation area. The body was found in a rotting condition and emitting a strong odor.\r",{"entities":[[13,25,"GPE"]]}],["\"Flash floods hit two villages in Central Aceh, namely Telege Sari Village and Gegarang Village, Jagong Jeget District.\"\r",{"entities":[[34,46,"GPE"],[55,74,"LOC"],[79,95,"LOC"],[97,118,"LOC"]]}],["A 2.5 year old child who was swept away by flash floods in Southeast Aceh was found dead. The boy was found this afternoon with his body covered in mud.\r",{"entities":[[59,73,"GPE"]]}],["\"Having remained at a fantastic price for a long time, now gold in East�Aceh�has fallen again. Gold seller at Toko Tiara, Mansur, explained that the decline in the price of gold occurred three days ago.\"\r",{"entities":[[67,80,"GPE"]]}],["A wild Sumatran elephant estimated to be 3-4 years old was killed by hunters in North Aceh. The hunters killed the elephant to take its tusks.\r",{"entities":[[80,91,"GPE"]]}],["\"In this operation, the police arrested a suspect with the initials RS (41), a resident of Gelampang Wih Tenang Uken Village, Permata District, Bener Meriah Regency.\"\r",{"entities":[[101,124,"LOC"],[126,142,"LOC"],[144,164,"GPE"]]}],["\"A resident of Gampong Blang Mane Dua Meunasah, Simpang Mamplam District, Bireuen Regency, namely MK (26), was found dead after ending his life by hanging himself at around 13.00 WIB on Thursday 25 April 2024 at his home.\"\r",{"entities":[[15,46,"LOC"],[48,72,"LOC"],[74,89,"GPE"]]}],["\"Floods and landslides hit two villages in Gayo Lues, Aceh, due to heavy rain that hit the area. The disaster caused 18 houses to be damaged and roads were cut off at six points.\"\r",{"entities":[[43,52,"GPE"],[54,58,"GPE"]]}],["\"Suspected of committing the crime of gambling (maisir), the Police Criminal Investigation Unit Opsnal Team arrested seven men while they were enjoying playing cards in Gampong Kuta Baro Jeuram, Senagan District, Nagan Raya.\"\r",{"entities":[[169,193,"LOC"],[195,211,"LOC"],[213,223,"GPE"]]}],["\"The results of monitoring the price of gold at the Beureunuen shopping market center, Pidie Regency, Thursday (25/4/2024) today, it turns out that the price has not changed.\"\r",{"entities":[[52,85,"LOC"],[87,100,"GPE"]]}],["\"It's just that at the peak of Kartini Day, activities are concentrated at the Trienggadeng Community Health Center, which is a location in the middle of Pidie Jaya district.\"\r",{"entities":[[79,115,"LOC"]]}],["\"When contacted, the former PDKS Main Director, Thursday (25/11) via cellular connection admitted that he was in Banda Aceh, \"\"God willing, we are ready, we just want to know first what about the people of Simeulue, do they want our figure?\"\" he answered diplomatically.\"\r",{"entities":[[113,123,"LOC"],[206,214,"GPE"]]}],["\"So we facilitated the execution of caning sentences by the prosecutor's office, there were two couples who were caned today. That was what the Head of the Islamic Sharia Enforcement Division of Satpol PP/WH, Roslina, said in Banda Aceh, Thursday (25/4/2024).\"\r",{"entities":[[209,216,"PERSON"],[226,236,"GPE"]]}],["\"After the spread, the price of red chilies decreased in Langsa City. Previously it was sold for IDR 50 thousand, today it is sold for IDR 33 thousand per kilogram.\"\r",{"entities":[[57,69,"GPE"]]}],["\"The price of gold in Lhokseumawe City on Friday (26/4/2024) rose today, compared to the price the previous day.\"\r",{"entities":[[22,38,"GPE"]]}],["\"A total of 17,922 people were recorded as having traveled to Weh Island, Sabang, Aceh, during the holidays and holidays with Eid al-Fitr 1445 Hijriah/2024 AD.\"\r",{"entities":[[62,72,"LOC"],[74,80,"GPE"],[82,86,"GPE"]]}],["\"The efforts of the joint Search and Rescue (SAR) team involved in searching for three landslide victims in Subulussalam, Subulussalam City, Aceh Province, were finally stopped.\"\r",{"entities":[[108,120,"GPE"],[122,139,"GPE"],[141,154,"GPE"]]}],["\"The police will summon the organizers of the night market in Kisaran, Asahan Regency, North Sumatra (North Sumatra) after bringing in a DJ and causing a vulgar dancing stage act to go viral. The reason is that the vulgar DJ entertainment activities were held in open public spaces.\"\r",{"entities":[[71,85,"GPE"],[87,100,"GPE"],[102,115,"GPE"]]}],["\"Irfan revealed that before being arrested, the five perpetrators carried out a robbery against a truck driver loaded with palm oil on the Sumatra (Jalinsum) highway, specifically Sei Balai Village, Batubara Regency.\"\r",{"entities":[[180,197,"LOC"],[199,215,"GPE"]]}],["\"A man in Dairi Regency, North Sumatra (North Sumatra) named Budi Liyanda (30) cheated and took away Rp. 100 million from selling corn. The police also arrested Budi in this case.\"\r",{"entities":[[10,23,"GPE"],[25,38,"GPE"],[40,53,"GPE"],[61,73,"PERSON"],[161,165,"PERSON"]]}],["\"The sky in Candirejo Village, Biru-biru District, Deli Serdang, was starting to get dark even though it was still 4 in the afternoon. Herlina started to get busy lifting the rigen or coaster to dry the opak.\"\r",{"entities":[[12,29,"LOC"],[31,49,"LOC"],[51,63,"GPE"]]}],["\"Lisna Manurung (30), a resident of Humbang Hasundutan, North Sumatra was found dead unnaturally at her home on Tuesday (26/12/2023).\"\r",{"entities":[[1,15,"PERSON"],[36,54,"GPE"],[56,69,"GPE"]]}],["Karo Regency is one of the areas in North Sumatra (North Sumatra) which is rich in tourist attractions. Having cool air can make tourists who come pamper themselves and linger in the highland area.\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"GPE"],[36,49,"GPE"],[51,64,"GPE"]]}],["\"Viral on social media, a grandfather named Marhan Harahap (66) died after being blocked by security officers when he was about to enter the mosque for Friday prayers at the same time as President Jokowi's work visit in Labuhanbatu, North Sumatra. The palace also opened its voice regarding this matter.\"\r",{"entities":[[44,58,"PERSON"],[187,203,"PERSON"],[220,231,"GPE"],[233,247,"GPE"]]}],["\"A drug dealer named Faisal (28) died after being arrested in Kampung Banjar I, Kota Pinang District, South Labuhanbatu Regency (Labusel). The police also explained the cause of Faisal's death.\"\r",{"entities":[[21,27,"GPE"],[62,78,"LOC"],[80,100,"LOC"],[102,127,"GPE"],[129,136,"GPE"],[178,184,"PERSON"]]}],["\"A man in North Labuhanbatu Regency (Labura), North Sumatra (North Sumatra) Suwanda (27) robbed a woman named Salmah (41). The perpetrator intercepted the victim and pointed a knife at him.\"\r",{"entities":[[10,35,"GPE"],[37,43,"GPE"],[46,59,"GPE"],[61,74,"GPE"],[76,83,"PERSON"],[110,116,"PERSON"]]}],["A girl in Langkat Regency was the victim of sexual abuse by four teenagers. The perpetrators committed sexual abuse in the warehouse and house.\r",{"entities":[[10,25,"GPE"]]}],["\"Bobby Nasution's billboard with Endar Sutan Lubis who is the Head of the Medan Bapenda and Muhammad Fadli Nasution who is the Chair of Koum Bobby which is a mejeng volunteer group in Panyabungan, Mandailing Natal Regency (Madina). The billboard contains greetings for Eid al-Fitr 1445 Hijriyah.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,15,"PERSON"],[33,50,"PERSON"],[92,115,"PERSON"],[184,195,"LOC"],[197,221,"GPE"],[223,229,"GPE"]]}],["\"Dozens of church members in Huliduho District, Nias Regency, North Sumatra (North Sumatra) experienced food poisoning during Easter services. Now, the police are still investigating the matter.\"\r",{"entities":[[29,46,"LOC"],[48,60,"GPE"],[62,75,"GPE"],[77,90,"GPE"]]}],["An earthquake measuring 5.0 magnitude rocked West Nias Regency this afternoon. The earthquake occurred at 11.45 WIB.\r",{"entities":[[45,62,"GPE"]]}],["\"The principal of Siduaori Vocational School 1, SZ (37), was reported for alleged abuse of his student, Yaredi Nduru (17), in South Nias Regency, North Sumatra (North Sumatra). Currently, the police have named SZ as a suspect.\"\r",{"entities":[[104,116,"PERSON"],[126,144,"GPE"],[146,159,"GPE"],[161,174,"GPE"]]}],["\"IH alias Ama Emki (45) surrendered herself to police officers after slashing her neighbor in North Nias Regency, North Sumatra named Simoni Harefa (36). IH surrendered himself after running away.\"\r",{"entities":[[10,18,"PERSON"],[94,112,"GPE"],[114,127,"GPE"],[134,147,"PERSON"]]}],["\"The arrest of Bunga took place in Padang Lawas Regency, North Sumatra Province (North Sumatra), Tuesday (28/11/2023) evening.\"\r",{"entities":[[15,20,"PERSON"],[35,55,"GPE"],[57,79,"GPE"],[81,94,"GPE"]]}],["\"A Land Rover pickup collided with a motorbike in North Padang Lawas Regency (Paluta), North Sumatra (North Sumatra). As a result of this incident, two teenagers were reported dead.\"\r",{"entities":[[50,76,"GPE"],[78,84,"GPE"],[87,100,"GPE"],[102,115,"GPE"]]}],["\"A car plunged into a ravine 100 meters deep on the Dairi-Pakpak Bharat Highway, precisely in Sukaramai District, Pakpak Bharat Regency, North Sumatra, Monday (28/11/2022).\"\r",{"entities":[[94,112,"LOC"],[114,135,"GPE"],[137,150,"GPE"]]}],["\"In a workshop in Samosir Regency, North Sumatra (Sumut), the fire was allegedly caused by an electrical short circuit. There were three cars and a motorbike involved in the incident that caught fire.\"\r",{"entities":[[18,33,"GPE"],[35,48,"GPE"],[50,55,"GPE"]]}],["\"Police arrested a man named Indra (35) for snatching the cell phone of a truck driver named Muhammad Fikri (21) in Serdang Bedagai (Sergai), North Sumatra (North Sumatra). At the time of the incident, the victim was parking his truck.\"\r",{"entities":[[29,34,"PERSON"],[93,107,"PERSON"],[116,131,"GPE"],[133,139,"GPE"],[142,155,"GPE"],[157,170,"GPE"]]}],["\"Former village head or pangulu in Simalungun Regency, North Sumatra (North Sumatra) Haryo Guntoro (53) is suspected of corruption in village funds amounting to IDR 337 million. From the results of the investigation, the perpetrator used the money for extravagance.\"\r",{"entities":[[35,53,"GPE"],[55,68,"GPE"],[70,83,"GPE"],[85,98,"PERSON"]]}],["\"South Tapanuli Regency (Tapsel) is one of the best areas in reducing the prevalence of stunting in North Sumatra, up to 23.8 percent.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,23,"GPE"],[25,31,"GPE"],[100,113,"GPE"]]}],["\"Police arrested a couple and their partner for killing a driver named Hasriano Tampubolon (47) at Kalangan Beach, Central Tapanuli Regency. The perpetrator's motive was hurt and revenge because the victim threatened to make their nasty video viral.\"\r",{"entities":[[71,90,"PERSON"],[99,113,"LOC"],[115,140,"GPE"]]}],["\"A video showing a woman being told to strip naked after being caught stealing potatoes went viral on social media. According to information, the incident occurred in North Tapanuli Regency (Taput), North Sumatra (North Sumatra).\"\r",{"entities":[[167,189,"GPE"],[191,196,"GPE"],[199,212,"GPE"],[214,227,"GPE"]]}],["Police searched the house of a woman with the initials RS alias Kanjeng Mami in Toba Samosir (Tobasa). The search was related to a case of suspected kidnapping and abuse.\r",{"entities":[[64,76,"PERSON"],[80,92,"GPE"],[94,100,"GPE"]]}],["\"A train bound for Medan-Binjai crashed into a truck loaded with sand which had broken down at a level crossing in Sumber Karya Village, Binjai City, North Sumatra. Luckily there were no fatalities or injuries as a result of this incident.\"\r",{"entities":[[115,135,"LOC"],[137,148,"GPE"],[150,164,"GPE"]]}],["\"Next, immediately take the victim's body to Thomson Gunungsitoli Hospital, in preparation for an autopsy which will be carried out by the North Sumatra Police Forensic Team, as well as carrying out an investigation to uncover the case.\"\r",{"entities":[]}],["\"A number of residents on Jalan H.M Yamin, Medan City, admitted that they had difficulty getting clean water as a result of the drainage project work in their area. The project is also said to have caused the cables on the side of the road to become increasingly chaotic.\"\r",{"entities":[[26,41,"LOC"],[43,53,"GPE"]]}],["Providing 10 hectares of land is a concrete step for the Padangsidimpuan City Government through the Padangsidimpuan City Agriculture Service to plant red chilies to control regional inflation in Padangsidimpuan City.\r",{"entities":[[196,216,"GPE"]]}],["\"Two public transportation drivers were involved in an argument and fight in Pematangsiantar City, North Sumatra (North Sumatra). One of them suffered cuts due to being hit by a sharp weapon (sajam).\"\r",{"entities":[[77,97,"GPE"],[99,112,"GPE"],[114,127,"GPE"]]}],["Sibolga City is a city in the province of North Sumatra which is located on the west coast of the island of Sumatra. This city stretches along the coast from north to south and is located in the Tapian Nauli Bay Area.\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"GPE"],[42,55,"GPE"],[108,116,"GPE"],[195,216,"LOC"]]}],["\"President Joko Widodo (Jokowi) today made a working visit to Tanjungbalai City, North Sumatra (North Sumatra) with a visit to the market to check the prices of a number of basic commodities (sembako) during the month of Ramadan. Jokowi, accompanied by PUPR Minister Basuki Hadimuljono, visited the Wire Market in Tanjungbalai.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,22,"PERSON"],[24,30,"PERSON"],[62,79,"GPE"],[81,94,"GPE"],[96,109,"GPE"],[230,236,"PERSON"],[267,285,"PERSON"],[314,326,"GPE"]]}],["\"An unemployed man with the initials MD (23) stole a sum of money and gold from a resident's house in Tebing Tinggi, North Sumatra (North Sumatra). After stealing, the perpetrator sold the stolen goods to go on an online gambling spree.\"\r",{"entities":[[102,115,"GPE"],[117,130,"GPE"],[132,145,"GPE"]]}],["\"A resident of Agam, West Sumatra (Sumbar) died after being struck by lightning. The incident occurred when the victim wanted to fertilize his corn seeds in the rice field.\"\r",{"entities":[[15,19,"GPE"],[21,33,"GPE"],[35,41,"GPE"]]}],["\"Actions of armed robbery occurred again in West Sumatra (Sumbar). This time, two perpetrators held gunpoint and scared the owner of a grocery shop in Jorong Sungai Nili, Nagari Sungai Kambut, Pulau Punjung District, Dharmasraya Regency.\"\r",{"entities":[[44,56,"GPE"],[58,64,"GPE"],[151,169,"LOC"],[171,191,"LOC"],[193,215,"LOC"],[217,236,"GPE"]]}],["West Sumatra is one of the provinces in Indonesia which is a favorite for local and foreign tourists to visit. There are various amazing tourist destinations in West Sumatra. One of them is the Mentawai Islands which have recently been in the public spotlight.\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"GPE"],[40,49,"GPE"],[161,174,"GPE"],[194,210,"GPE"]]}],["\"He explained that FE forced his stepson three times at home, Suliki District, Limapuluh Kota Regency. Inspector Hendra said that FE committed this depraved act in July 2023 in the afternoon at around 15.30 WIB.\"\r",{"entities":[[62,77,"LOC"],[79,102,"GPE"]]}],["\"Brothers with the initials AM (65) and T (68) in Padang Pariaman, West Sumatra (Sumbar) were involved in a duel. As a result, T died after being attacked by the perpetrator. The duel between the two perpetrators was allegedly triggered by economic motives.\"\r",{"entities":[[50,65,"GPE"],[67,79,"GPE"],[81,87,"GPE"]]}],["\"With the acquisition of these 6 seats, Sabar categorized the Democrats as having entered the top tier of parties in Pasaman.\"\r",{"entities":[[117,124,"GPE"]]}],["\"Yusuf, a resident of Kinali District, West Pasaman, South Sumatra (Sumsel), was seriously injured after being attacked by a crocodile while fetching water from a river.\"\r",{"entities":[[22,37,"LOC"],[39,51,"GPE"],[53,66,"GPE"],[68,74,"GPE"]]}],["\"Hundreds of residents affected by the flash flood disaster in Nagari Nanggalo, Koto XI Tarusan District, Pesisir Selatan Regency, West Sumatra, demonstrated at the sub-district office today.\"\r",{"entities":[[63,78,"LOC"],[80,104,"LOC"],[106,129,"GPE"],[131,143,"GPE"]]}],["\"The deception of JR (29) and AB (41), two women from Sijunjung Regency, West Sumatra (Sumbar) offering jobs to Malaysia was exposed.\"\r",{"entities":[[54,71,"GPE"],[73,85,"GPE"],[87,93,"GPE"],[112,120,"GPE"]]}],["\"A family from Solok, West Sumatra (Sumbar) died in a car in Bungo, Jambi. They allegedly died because they inhaled carbon dioxide gas (CO2) from inside the car due to air conditioning circulation.\"\r",{"entities":[[22,34,"GPE"],[36,42,"GPE"],[61,66,"GPE"],[68,74,"GPE"]]}],["\"People with Mental Disorders (ODGJ) with the initials FA went on a rampage in Jorong Ampalu Nagari Alam Pauh Duo, Pauh Duo District, South Solok Regency, West Sumatra. One person was injured as a result of ODGJ's rampage.\"\r",{"entities":[[79,113,"LOC"],[115,132,"LOC"],[134,153,"GPE"],[155,168,"GPE"]]}],["\"A drainage cleaning worker in Kelok Hantu, Nagari Aie Angek, X Koto District, Tanah Datar, West Sumatra (Sumbar) was killed by the cold lava flood of Mount Marapi. The victim died after being trapped in an excavator when a flood of cold lava occurred.\"\r",{"entities":[[31,42,"LOC"],[44,60,"LOC"],[62,77,"LOC"],[79,90,"LOC"],[92,104,"GPE"],[106,112,"GPE"],[151,164,"LOC"]]}],["\"State Minister for BUMN Erick Thohir and member of Commission VI DPR-RI Andre Rosiade inaugurated the culinary area in Bukittinggi City, West Sumatra. The culinary area was built using the former Lambuang Station area owned by PT KAI.\"\r",{"entities":[[25,37,"PERSON"],[73,86,"PERSON"],[120,136,"GPE"],[138,151,"GPE"],[197,213,"LOC"],[228,234,"ORG"]]}],["\"The Padang City Agriculture Service noted that in 2024 rice fields in Padang City will shrink by 1,000 hectares compared to 2019.\"\r",{"entities":[[71,82,"GPE"]]}],["\"A seven year old girl, HKL, in Padang Panjang, West Sumatra (Sumbar) almost became a victim of kidnapping. Perpetrator J (37) was determined to kidnap HKL because he was in debt of tens of millions of rupiah.\"\r",{"entities":[[32,46,"GPE"],[48,60,"GPE"],[62,68,"GPE"]]}],["\"A man with the initials Z (47) in Pariaman City, West Sumatra (Sumbar) was arrested by the police after molesting and having sex with his 5 year old nephew. The perpetrator molested the victim while he was playing with his child.\"\r",{"entities":[[35,48,"GPE"],[50,62,"GPE"],[64,70,"GPE"]]}],["\"A video showing students committing lewd acts in Batang Agam Park, Payakumbuh City, West Sumatra (Sumbar) caused a stir among local residents. After the video went viral, the Payakumbuh City Satpol PP immediately went to the location to check on it.\"\r",{"entities":[[50,66,"LOC"],[68,83,"GPE"],[85,97,"GPE"],[99,105,"GPE"]]}],["\"Kasatreskrim Sawahlunto Police, AKP Syafrinaldi said the process of dismantling the grave is currently underway at Cemara TPU, Sawahlunto. Meanwhile, the demolition was witnessed directly by Iwan's family.\"\r",{"entities":[[33,48,"PERSON"],[116,126,"LOC"],[128,139,"GPE"],[192,196,"PERSON"]]}],["\"The police succeeded in arresting a 27 year old young man, Arianto, also known as Kaliang, in connection with a motorbike theft case in Lubuk Selasih, Solok Regency.\"\r",{"entities":[[60,67,"PERSON"],[83,90,"PERSON"],[137,150,"LOC"],[152,165,"GPE"]]}],["The statue of Bung Karno in Banyuasin has now been declared similar. This is based on the results of a poll conducted by the Banyuasin Regency Government which was distributed via WhatsApp message.\r",{"entities":[[28,37,"GPE"]]}],["\"The police have named Hanapin (56), the farmer who killed his ODGJ brother-in-law, in Empat Lawang, as a suspect. Hanapin admitted that before the murder occurred, he had thrown the victim out of the house.\"\r",{"entities":[[23,30,"PERSON"],[87,99,"GPE"],[115,122,"PERSON"]]}],["A teenager in Lahat with the initials AG (14) was battered and his right leg was peeling after being beaten while hanging out. The student was assaulted for being impolite and responded by glaring after being reprimanded for repeatedly blowing cigarette smoke at the perpetrator.\r",{"entities":[[14,19,"GPE"]]}],["\"The Kijang car was modified to transport pertalite illegally in Muara Enim, South Sumatra (Sumsel). A resident with the initials A was arrested and named a suspect after his Kijang car exploded and caught fire at a gas station.\"\r",{"entities":[[65,75,"LOC"],[77,90,"GPE"],[92,98,"GPE"]]}],["\"The news of the appearance of wild bears caused a stir among the residents of Cinta Damai Hamlet (C1), Sungai Lilin District, Musi Banyuasin (Muba). Residents' activities in oil palm plantations are limited, because they are increasing their vigilance.\"\r",{"entities":[[79,97,"LOC"],[104,125,"LOC"],[127,141,"GPE"],[143,147,"GPE"]]}],["\"The police have named M Yasin alias MY (38), who raped his stepson, B (15), until she was 6 months pregnant in Musi Rawas (Mura), as a suspect. During the year of raping his stepson, Yasin carried out his depraved actions by threatening to divorce the victim's mother.\"\r",{"entities":[[23,30,"PERSON"],[112,122,"GPE"],[124,128,"GPE"],[184,189,"PERSON"]]}],["\"The flash flood disaster that occurred in North Musi Rawas (Muratara), South Sumatra (Sumsel) was submerged in 48 villages in 5 sub-districts. It starts to recede and gradually returns to normal.\"\r",{"entities":[[43,59,"GPE"],[61,69,"GPE"],[72,85,"GPE"],[87,93,"GPE"]]}],["\"Nazwa Keyza Safira (19), the daughter of a TNI soldier, was stabbed to death by a mugger in Tanjung Senai, Ogan Ilir Regency, South Sumatra, Friday (2/2/2024) evening.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,19,"PERSON"],[93,106,"LOC"],[108,125,"GPE"],[127,140,"GPE"]]}],["\"The defendant Andri Triyono, a bank employee in Ogan Komering Ilir, South Sumatra, was sentenced to 9 years in prison. He was charged with stealing customer funds.\"\r",{"entities":[[15,28,"PERSON"],[49,67,"GPE"],[69,82,"GPE"]]}],["\"The police have arrested Zulkapun (43), who hacked a young man named Rolis (19), almost to death in Ogan Komering Ulu (OKU), South Sumatra. To the police, Zul admitted that he was actually hurt by Rolis' father, who had been having an affair with his wife.\"\r",{"entities":[[26,34,"PERSON"],[70,75,"PERSON"],[101,118,"GPE"],[120,123,"GPE"],[126,140,"GPE"],[156,159,"PERSON"],[198,203,"PERSON"]]}],["\"Residents of South Ogan Komering Ulu (OKU), South Sumatra, were shocked by a sadistic stabbing incident in one of the residents' houses. The victim, Ade Indra Maulana (28), was reportedly almost killed by being hacked blindly by his own colleague.\"\r",{"entities":[[14,37,"GPE"],[39,42,"GPE"],[45,58,"GPE"],[150,167,"PERSON"]]}],["\"The East Ogan Komering Ulu Resort Police, South Sumatra, are hunting for the Putra Sulung bus driver and attendant who fled after their vehicle was involved in an accident with a train, resulting in the death of a passenger, Sunday (21/4).\"\r",{"entities":[[1,41,"ORG"],[43,56,"GPE"]]}],["\"Hundreds of residents' houses in 10 villages in Tanah Abang and Penukal Districts, Penukal Abab Lematang Ilir (PALI) Regency, South Sumatra were hit by flooding. This disaster occurred due to the overflow of the Lematang River, which experienced an increase in discharge.\"\r",{"entities":[[49,60,"LOC"],[65,82,"LOC"],[84,110,"GPE"],[112,116,"GPE"],[127,140,"GPE"],[213,227,"LOC"]]}],["\"A vocational school student in Lubuklinggau, South Sumatra, was crushed to death by a truck while pushing his motorbike which had broken down. Currently the police are still investigating the incident.\"\r",{"entities":[[32,44,"GPE"],[46,59,"GPE"]]}],["\"Small hailstones occurred in Pagar Alam City, South Sumatra (Sumsel). The Meteorology, Climatology and Geophysics Agency (BMKG) said the hail incident occurred because we have now entered the transition season.\"\r",{"entities":[[30,45,"GPE"],[47,60,"GPE"],[62,68,"GPE"]]}],["\"A housewife (IRT) in Palembang, South Sumatra (Sumsel) named Mila Karmila (31) reported a theft that occurred in her house. Not just once, he admitted that his house had been burgled 10 times.\"\r",{"entities":[[22,31,"GPE"],[33,46,"GPE"],[48,54,"GPE"],[62,74,"PERSON"]]}],["\"Residents of Prabumulih, South Sumatra were shocked by the discovery of a man with the initials AS (31) hanging dead in his room. AS allegedly committed suicide because he was in debt and ashamed of his mother.\"\r",{"entities":[[14,24,"GPE"],[26,39,"GPE"]]}],["The Riau Regional Police won a pre-trial lawsuit against a state-owned bank corruption suspect worth more than IDR 46 billion in Bengkalis. This means that ER is still being detained as a legal suspect and perpetrator.\r",{"entities":[[129,139,"GPE"]]}],["\"A man who was a former rehabilitator for drug cases in Indragiri Hilir (Inhil), Riau, has been arrested again by the police. This man with the initials FL was arrested because he brandished a machete at the police after being arrested for revenge.\"\r",{"entities":[[56,71,"GPE"],[73,78,"GPE"],[81,85,"GPE"]]}],["\"A woman named Alfi Naradipta (21) in Indragiri Hulu, Riau was arrested by the police. He was arrested because he was determined to hit his grandmother on the head until she almost died in order to control her property.\"\r",{"entities":[[15,29,"PERSON"],[38,52,"GPE"],[54,58,"GPE"]]}],["\"The mutual reporting action took place between two farmer groups in Kampar Regency, Riau. The two of them reported it to the police after both admitting to being victims of a beating.\"\r",{"entities":[[69,83,"GPE"],[85,90,"GPE"]]}],["\"Forest and land fires (karhutla) still occur in Riau Province. This time, peat land burned badly in Penyagun Village, Rangsang District, Meranti Islands Regency. On Saturday (23/3/2024) evening, a burning fire engulfed the peatland bushland.\"\r",{"entities":[[49,63,"GPE"],[101,117,"LOC"],[119,136,"LOC"],[138,162,"GPE"]]}],["\"An earthquake measuring magnitude (M) 5.8 rocked the Kuantan Singingi area, Riau this afternoon. The earthquake reportedly did not have the potential for a tsunami.\"\r",{"entities":[[54,70,"GPE"],[77,81,"GPE"]]}],["\"This accusation apparently made Herman furious and did not accept it. He also brutally murdered his wife at her brother's house, in Pangkalan Lesung, Pelalawan, Riau. The murder occurred last Wednesday (14/4/2024). Before Mona was stabbed to death, the two of them had an argument.\"\r",{"entities":[[133,149,"LOC"],[151,160,"GPE"],[162,167,"GPE"]]}],["\"From the photo received by detikSumut on Wednesday (17/4/2024), Arif was seen wearing an orange prison jumpsuit. The resident of Rokan Hilir (Rohil) Regency was photographed with a yellow background.\"\r",{"entities":[[65,69,"PERSON"],[130,141,"GPE"],[143,148,"GPE"]]}],["\"A teenager named Fahru Rozi (17) in Rokan Hulu, Riau, died after being slashed by his friend. He was slashed because he was suspected of stealing rice beans or palm oil belonging to the perpetrator, TL (20).\"\r",{"entities":[[18,28,"PERSON"],[37,47,"GPE"],[49,53,"GPE"]]}],["\"The Riau Natural Resources Conservation Center (BBKSDA) evacuated a sun bear from Sabak Auh Village, Siak, Riau. The evacuation was carried out after the sun bear attacked the residents' livestock.\"\r",{"entities":[[83,100,"LOC"],[102,106,"GPE"],[108,113,"GPE"]]}],["\"Two owners of methamphetamine drugs in Dumai, Riau, with the initials ZA (46) and MI (27), were arrested by the police. The two perpetrators were arrested when they picked up 5 kg of methamphetamine from Malaysia.\"\r",{"entities":[[40,45,"GPE"],[47,51,"GPE"],[205,213,"GPE"]]}],["\"Two debt collectors with the initials PR (22) and IA (18) who went viral blocking cars on the streets of Pekanbaru were arrested. However, recently the car driver who was confronted by the debt collector did not want to prolong the problem.\"\r",{"entities":[]}],["\"For those of you who are looking for a cheap house, you can check Bintan Regency, Riau Islands. House prices there start from IDR 150 million.\"\r",{"entities":[[67,81,"GPE"],[83,96,"GPE"]]}],["\"Karimun Police thwarted an attempt to smuggle six prospective illegal Indonesian Migrant Workers (PMI) from West Nusa Tenggara (NTB) to Malaysia in Karimun Regency, Riau Islands (Kepri). One crew member with the initials I (48) was named a suspect.\"\r",{"entities":[[109,127,"GPE"],[137,145,"GPE"],[149,164,"GPE"],[166,178,"GPE"]]}],["\"Heavy rain that fell on Anambas and Natuna Regencies, Riau Islands Province (Kepri), since Sunday (19/11) afternoon resulted in flooding in a number of areas. It was recorded that more than hundreds of people were affected by flooding in the two districts.\"\r",{"entities":[[25,32,"GPE"],[37,53,"GPE"],[55,76,"GPE"],[78,83,"GPE"]]}],["\"A young man with the initials A (19) in Dabo Singkep, Lingga Regency, Riau Islands was arrested by the police. The perpetrator was arrested for molesting his underage girlfriend while drunk.\"\r",{"entities":[[41,53,"LOC"],[55,69,"GPE"],[71,83,"GPE"]]}],["\"Heavy rain that fell on Anambas and Natuna Regencies, Riau Islands Province (Kepri), since Sunday (19/11) afternoon resulted in flooding in a number of areas. It was recorded that more than hundreds of people were affected by flooding in the two districts.\"\r",{"entities":[[25,32,"GPE"],[37,53,"GPE"],[55,76,"GPE"],[78,83,"GPE"]]}],["\"A man with the initials AR (26) was determined to steal his boss's pickup car in Sagulung District, Batam, Riau Islands (Kepri). The perpetrator then created a scenario pretending to find the car and asked for IDR 20 million in return.\"\r",{"entities":[[82,99,"LOC"],[101,106,"GPE"],[108,120,"GPE"],[122,127,"GPE"]]}],["\"A household assistant (ART) in Tanjungpinang, Riau Islands (Kepri), was arrested by the police for stealing her employer's money and jewelry. The total money and jewelry taken by the perpetrator reached IDR 100 million.\"\r",{"entities":[[32,45,"GPE"],[47,59,"GPE"],[61,66,"GPE"]]}],["\"The case of the death of a girl named Nasifa (20) who was found dead in a brick excavation pool in Batanghari, Jambi, has not been revealed. It has been almost two months since the case has been under investigation by the Batanghari Police.\"\r",{"entities":[[39,45,"PERSON"],[100,110,"GPE"],[112,117,"GPE"]]}],["\"Head of the Jambi Basarnas Operations Sub-Section, Kornelis, said that almost 20,000 people or 19,292 people in Bungo Regency were flood victims.\"\r",{"entities":[[52,60,"PERSON"],[113,126,"GPE"]]}],["\"A pickup truck had a single accident on the Bangmo-Kerinci Cross Road, Muara Emat Village, Batang Merangin District, Kerinci, Jambi. The accident occurred allegedly because the driver was speeding and lost control and fell into a 45 meter deep ravine.\"\r",{"entities":[[45,70,"LOC"],[72,90,"LOC"],[92,116,"LOC"],[118,125,"GPE"],[127,133,"GPE"]]}],["\"A middle-aged widower in Merangin, Jambi, USA (58) was arrested by the police after raping a woman with mental disabilities in an empty house. Currently, the perpetrator is still being investigated by the police.\"\r",{"entities":[[26,34,"GPE"],[36,41,"GPE"]]}],["\"Two robbers of oil palm trader Gunawan (27), on Jalan Lintas Jambi-Muaro Sabak, Muaro Jambi Regency, apparently had been stalking the victim while he was at the bank. The perpetrator pretends to be a customer.\"\r",{"entities":[[32,39,"PERSON"],[49,79,"LOC"],[81,100,"GPE"]]}],["\"Two men claiming to be journalists and members of the National Police were arrested by the police after blackmailing residents of Sarolangun, Jambi. The perpetrator blackmailed the victim who wanted to fill up with fuel at a gas station and was accused of being a fuel dealer.\"\r",{"entities":[[131,141,"GPE"],[143,149,"GPE"]]}],["\"Kuntoro Yono (30) had the heart to kill his wife Liza Astuti (31) on an oil palm plantation. This murder was triggered by a domestic dispute. The bloody incident occurred in Rantau Benar Village, Renah Mendaluh District, West Tanjung Jabung Regency (West Tanjab), on Sunday (17/3/20224), at around 12.00 WIB\"\r",{"entities":[[1,13,"PERSON"],[50,61,"PERSON"],[175,195,"LOC"],[197,220,"LOC"],[222,249,"GPE"],[251,262,"GPE"]]}],["\"A fire occurred at the Regional Financial Agency (Bakeuda) Office of East Tanjung Jabung Regency, Jambi, Sunday (11/2/2024) at around 13.45 WIB. The incident is thought to have occurred due to an electrical short circuit or short circuit.\"\r",{"entities":[[70,97,"GPE"],[99,104,"GPE"]]}],["\"The killer of Airul Harahap (13), a student in Tebo, Jambi was sentenced to 7.5 years in prison. Airul's family expressed disappointment with the verdict.\"\r",{"entities":[[15,28,"PERSON"],[48,52,"GPE"],[54,59,"GPE"],[98,103,"GPE"]]}],["\"A fire occurred at the Regional Financial Agency (Bakeuda) Office of East Tanjung Jabung Regency, Jambi, Sunday (11/2/2024) at around 13.45 WIB. The incident is thought to have occurred due to an electrical short circuit or short circuit.\"\r",{"entities":[[70,97,"GPE"],[99,104,"GPE"]]}],["\"An illegal gold panner named Edi Suparman (35), a resident of Sungai Banyak City, Jambi, was reportedly swept away while working to pan for gold. A SAR team was sent to carry out a search.\"\r",{"entities":[[30,42,"PERSON"],[63,81,"GPE"],[83,88,"GPE"]]}],["\"A tectonic earthquake with a strength of M 5.6 that rocked the southwest of South Bengkulu caused one resident's house to be damaged. Luckily, the owner of the house in South Bengkulu Regency was safe and was not crushed by the building.\"\r",{"entities":[[64,91,"LOC"],[170,192,"GPE"]]}],["\"For those of you who are looking for a cheap house, you can really check the following information. In Central Bengkulu Regency, Bengkulu there are still many houses with prices starting from IDR 100 million that can be found.\"\r",{"entities":[[104,128,"GPE"],[130,138,"GPE"]]}],["\"Four traffic controllers or Pak Ogahs in North Bengkulu were arrested by the police after abusing a bus attendant and box driver. Currently, the perpetrators have been arrested and face up to 12 years in prison.\"\r",{"entities":[[42,56,"GPE"]]}],["\"Natural tourism in Kaur Regency has a variety of beauty. There are beaches with fine white sand and uniquely shaped rocks, and there are also lakes that are still very natural.\"\r",{"entities":[[20,32,"GPE"]]}],["\"Affordable houses are certainly the target of many people. For those of you who are looking for a cheap house, you can check in Kepahiang Regency, Bengkulu. House prices there start from IDR 120 million.\"\r",{"entities":[[129,146,"GPE"],[148,157,"GPE"]]}],["\"Rain was still pouring even though dawn had just broken at around 05.40 WIB, Tuesday (16/4/2024), in Lebong Regency, Bengkulu Province.\"\r",{"entities":[[102,116,"GPE"],[118,135,"GPE"]]}],["\"A 5.1 magnitude earthquake rocked the Mukomuko area, Bengkulu on Thursday (24/11/2022) at around 09.11 WIB.\"\r",{"entities":[[39,47,"GPE"],[54,62,"GPE"]]}],["\"In Rejang Lebong Regency, Bengkulu, there are still houses with large plots of land whose prices start from IDR 120 million. For that price, you can get a house with 170 m2 of land, you know!\"\r",{"entities":[[4,25,"GPE"],[27,35,"GPE"]]}],["\"A M 3.3 earthquake occurred in Seluma, Bengkulu. The earthquake did not cause the potential for a tsunami.\"\r",{"entities":[[32,38,"GPE"],[40,49,"GPE"]]}],["\"A M 3.3 earthquake occurred in Seluma, Bengkulu. The earthquake did not cause the potential for a tsunami.\"\r",{"entities":[[32,38,"GPE"],[40,49,"GPE"]]}],["\"The price of granulated sugar in Bangka Regency, Bangka Belitung Islands Province, has not increased.\"\r",{"entities":[[34,48,"GPE"],[50,82,"GPE"]]}],["\"The perpetrator who was successfully arrested was Suryanto alias Belande (34), a resident of Hamlet 1 Rambat, Rambat Village, Simpang Teritip District, West Bangka Regency.\"\r",{"entities":[[51,59,"PERSON"],[66,73,"PERSON"],[94,109,"LOC"],[111,125,"LOC"],[127,151,"LOC"],[153,172,"GPE"]]}],["\"Martua Carolus Silaban (60), a petai farmer in South Bangka (Basel) Regency, suffered stab wounds from the head to the back after a duel with 2 thieves in his garden. The victim was rushed to South Bangka Hospital.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,23,"PERSON"],[48,60,"GPE"],[62,67,"GPE"]]}],["\"Taufik (47), the Mitsubishi truck driver who hit an elementary school boy in Central Bangka Regency named Adiba (7) has been arrested by the police. The police said that Taufik was still undergoing examination at the Central Bangka Police Traffic Office.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,7,"PERSON"],[78,100,"GPE"],[107,112,"PERSON"],[171,177,"PERSON"]]}],["\"The Belitung Regency Education and Culture Service (Disdikbud) plans to regroup elementary schools on Buntar Island, Selat Nasik District, Belitung Regency, Bangka Belitung Islands Province.\"\r",{"entities":[[103,116,"LOC"],[118,138,"LOC"],[140,156,"GPE"],[158,190,"GPE"]]}],["\"Seven people who committed crimes in East Belitung (Beltim), Bangka Belitung Islands Province (Babel), were arrested by the Panah Satreskrim Polres Beltim team, Thursday (18/4/2024).\"\r",{"entities":[[38,51,"GPE"],[53,59,"GPE"],[62,94,"GPE"],[96,101,"GPE"]]}],["\"The five people, namely Basit Cinda, is an advertising entrepreneur in Pangkalpinang City. He was the first person to register.\"\r",{"entities":[[25,36,"PERSON"],[72,91,"GPE"]]}],["\"A young man in Central Lampung was stabbed to death by a sharp weapon. This incident occurred around the gas station on Jalan Lintas Sumatra, Kampung Terbanggi Agung, Gunung Sugih District, Central Lampung on Tuesday (23/4) evening.\"\r",{"entities":[[121,141,"LOC"],[143,166,"LOC"],[168,189,"LOC"],[191,206,"GPE"]]}],["\"The mastermind behind the rape and confinement of a junior high school student in North Lampung Regency was successfully arrested in Langon village, Tahunan District, Jepara Regency, Central Java.\"\r",{"entities":[[83,104,"GPE"],[134,148,"LOC"],[150,166,"LOC"],[168,182,"GPE"],[184,196,"GPE"]]}],["Pertamina Patra Niaga ensures the availability of 3 kilograms of LPG for the South Lampung area in safe conditions. Pertamina also asked official agents not to sell 3 Kilogram LPG above the Highest Retail Price (HET).\r",{"entities":[[0,21,"ORG"],[77,90,"GPE"]]}],["\"Five people who set wild boar traps in the Pekon South Lumbok coffee plantation area, Lumbok Seminung District, West Lampung Regency, were questioned by the police.\"\r",{"entities":[[87,111,"LOC"],[113,133,"GPE"]]}],["\"Dozens of residents of Sukadana District, East Lampung Regency criticized the local government for never repairing damaged roads.\"\r",{"entities":[[24,41,"LOC"],[43,63,"GPE"]]}],["\"Tragedy rocked Mesuji Regency, Lampung, after a 28 year old female teacher named Rosiya Aprilia was found dead in a tragic condition at her official residence in Bujung Buring Village, Mesuji Regency.\"\r",{"entities":[[16,30,"GPE"],[32,39,"GPE"],[82,96,"PERSON"],[163,184,"LOC"],[186,200,"GPE"]]}],["\"Lampung Police Chief Inspector General Helmy Santika asked his staff to take firm action against single organs that exceed operational hours according to regulations. This was the impact of a viral video of 2 teenagers reportedly dying of an overdose during a single organ activity in Tegineneng District, Pesawaran Regency, Sunday (18/2/2024).\"\r",{"entities":[[40,53,"PERSON"],[286,305,"LOC"],[307,324,"GPE"]]}],["\"The accident occurred on a forest slope in the Tebing Batu Manula area, Pekon Rata Agung, Lemong, Pesisir Barat on Friday (5/4/2024) afternoon.\"\r",{"entities":[[48,66,"LOC"],[73,89,"LOC"],[91,97,"LOC"],[99,112,"GPE"]]}],["\"The perpetrator of the mugging who took action on Jalan Pekon Sumberagung, Ambarawa, Pringsewu on Monday (22/4/2024) evening, was battered by the judgment of the residents.\"\r",{"entities":[[51,74,"LOC"],[76,84,"GPE"],[86,95,"GPE"]]}],["\"As many as 45 houses in Tulang Bawang Regency, Lampung Province were damaged by the tornado.\"\r",{"entities":[[25,46,"GPE"],[48,64,"GPE"]]}],["\"A man was found hanging himself dead in Tiyuh Sumber Rejeki, Gunung Agung District, West Tulang Bawang Regency, Thursday (25/1/2024) at 04.00 WIB.\"\r",{"entities":[[41,60,"LOC"],[62,83,"LOC"],[85,111,"GPE"]]}],["\"YD is suspected of deliberately secretly recording the bathing activities of a woman with the initials MA in Pekon Pardawaras, Semaka District, Tanggamus Regency, on Sunday (17/3/2024).\"\r",{"entities":[[110,126,"LOC"],[128,143,"LOC"],[145,162,"GPE"]]}],["\"An inspiring story comes from a police officer in Way Kanan Regency, Lampung Province named Minanto. The man with the rank of Aipda founded elementary school (SD) and junior high school (SMP) levels in Way Kanan Regency.\"\r",{"entities":[[51,68,"GPE"],[70,86,"GPE"],[93,101,"PERSON"],[203,220,"GPE"]]}],["A man in Bandar Lampung who claimed to be a member of the Marines was arrested by residents. The man named Didi Darmawan is said to have committed fraud against a woman he was dating and promised to marry.\r",{"entities":[[9,23,"GPE"],[107,120,"PERSON"]]}],["Seprita from TACB Metro said that since 2021 four cultural heritage sites have been designated in Metro City and in 2023 his party has resubmitted recommendations for designation for three cultural heritage sites.\r",{"entities":[]}],["\"Residents in Sukadasar Village, Warunggunung District, Lebak, Banten, protested against damaged roads by planting banana trees and stocking catfish. This action was taken because the road conditions had not been repaired.\"\r",{"entities":[[14,31,"LOC"],[33,54,"LOC"],[56,61,"GPE"],[63,69,"GPE"]]}],["\"A resident of Cihoe Village, Kertamukti Village, Sumur District, Pandeglang Regency, Banten named Dendi (30) was attacked by a crocodile while fishing on the coast of Cihoe. Fortunately, the victim's life was saved and he has now received medical treatment.\"\r",{"entities":[[15,28,"LOC"],[30,48,"LOC"],[50,64,"LOC"],[66,84,"GPE"],[86,92,"GPE"],[99,104,"PERSON"],[159,174,"LOC"]]}],["\"A number of victims of fraudulent investment fraud a few days ago just brought the perpetrator with the initials M (23), a resident of Pejaten Neighborhood, Kaligandu Village, Serang City, Banten to the Banten Regional Police.\"\r",{"entities":[[136,156,"LOC"],[158,175,"LOC"],[177,188,"GPE"],[190,196,"GPE"]]}],["Hospitality business actors are collaborating with MSMEs in Greater Tangerang to provide facilities for MSME products to be marketed in every hotel in Tangerang City.\r",{"entities":[[151,165,"GPE"]]}],["\"The peak event which will be held on May 6 2024 at Cilegon City Square will be enlivened by performances by artists from the capital city, Jamrud, and will be attended by a number of regional heads from various regions in Indonesia.\"\r",{"entities":[[52,71,"LOC"]]}],["\"The man with the initials AB alias Alex (43) doesn't seem to be deterred even though he has been imprisoned for four and a half years. This recidivist from Singarajan Village, Pontang District, Serang Regency was again arrested by the police because he was again distributing drugs.\"\r",{"entities":[[36,40,"PERSON"],[157,175,"LOC"],[177,193,"LOC"],[195,209,"GPE"]]}],["Hospitality business actors are collaborating with MSMEs in Greater Tangerang to provide facilities for MSME products to be marketed in every hotel in Tangerang City.\r",{"entities":[[151,165,"GPE"]]}],["\"Plans to extend the Jakarta MRT route to South Tangerang have emerged again. However, to be able to realize this public transportation project, the Ministry of Transportation said further studies were needed regarding the readiness of local regional governments (Pemda).\"\r",{"entities":[[42,57,"GPE"]]}],["\"Based on information, at the time of the incident Fikri and Ajis were returning home after delivering fish to Ujungberung Market, Bandung City to sell.\"\r",{"entities":[[51,56,"PERSON"],[61,65,"PERSON"],[111,129,"LOC"],[131,143,"GPE"]]}],["Heavy rain that poured down the West Bandung Regency (KBB) area and its surroundings on Friday (26/4/2024) afternoon caused trees to fall and cause landslides.\r",{"entities":[[32,52,"GPE"]]}],["\"Rini Mariany was found dead with her body stored in a suitcase in the Cikarang area, Bekasi Regency. Rini's funeral was filled with emotional tears from the family.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,13,"PERSON"],[71,79,"GPE"],[86,101,"GPE"]]}],["\"The head of the RW was involved in an argument with community health center officials in Leuwisadeng, Bogor Regency, West Java. The dispute was separated by a number of members of social organizations (ormas) and went viral on social media (medsos).\"\r",{"entities":[[90,101,"LOC"],[103,116,"GPE"],[118,128,"GPE"]]}],["\"This was conveyed by Siti Atikoh in front of participants in the NU Muslim gathering in Ciamis City and Banjar City, West Java, Tuesday (5/12/2023). Atikoh was in the two cities on the second day of the Political Safari.\"\r",{"entities":[[22,33,"PERSON"],[89,100,"GPE"],[105,116,"GPE"],[118,127,"GPE"],[150,156,"PERSON"]]}],["\"Cianjur Regency is one of the regions in Indonesia that has succeeded in making brilliant achievements regarding reducing stunting throughout 2022. Based on the results of the 2022 Indonesian Nutrition Status Survey (SSGI), the stunting prevalence rate in Cianjur fell to 13.6 percent from the previous 33.7 percent.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,16,"GPE"],[42,51,"GPE"],[257,264,"GPE"]]}],["\"The alleged rape case involving an underage girl occurred in Cirebon, West Java. Sadly, the alleged perpetrator in this case is the victim's stepfather.\"\r",{"entities":[[62,69,"GPE"],[71,81,"GPE"]]}],["\"People living on Jalan Ibrahim Aji, Tarogong District, Garut, West Java were shocked by the discovery of pork sellers on the Eid 2024 homecoming route.\"\r",{"entities":[[18,35,"LOC"],[37,54,"LOC"],[56,61,"GPE"],[63,72,"GPE"]]}],["\"Some farmers have started using drones to spray pesticides on their rice fields in Indramayu, West Java. The cost of using the drone is IDR 5 million per hectare.\"\r",{"entities":[[84,93,"GPE"],[95,105,"GPE"]]}],["The dengue fever case in Karawang is rampant. Hundreds of residents were recorded as being exposed to dengue fever and two people were declared dead.\r",{"entities":[[25,33,"GPE"]]}],["\"This tourist village on Jalan Sudi Mampir, Dusun Manis, Cikaso Village, Keramatmulya District, Kuningan Regency is proof that if Bumdes funds are managed well, they will produce products that have high selling value and become income for the village which in turn can generate income for the village. helping village development outside of village fund assistance.\"\r",{"entities":[[25,42,"LOC"],[44,55,"LOC"],[57,71,"LOC"],[73,94,"LOC"],[96,112,"GPE"]]}],["\"After completing his bicycle ride around Indonesia, Ari Yami has the ambition to continue his cycling journey from Majalengka in West Java to Mecca in Saudi Arabia to perform the Umrah.\"\r",{"entities":[[53,61,"PERSON"],[116,126,"GPE"],[130,139,"GPE"],[143,148,"GPE"],[152,164,"GPE"]]}],["The circulation of money during the 2024 Eid holiday in Pangandaran Regency is estimated to be quite large.\r",{"entities":[[56,75,"GPE"]]}],["\"A fallen tree hit a motorbike on Jalan Bukit Indah City Industrial Area, Bungunsari District, Purwakarta Regency. Two people died as a result of the incident.\"\r",{"entities":[[34,72,"LOC"],[74,93,"LOC"],[95,114,"GPE"]]}],["\"Yosep Hidayah, the defendant in the murder case of Tuti and Amalia Mustika Ratu or Amel in Subang Regency, was unsuccessful in his efforts to refute the charges. This was after Yosep's exception was rejected by the Panel of Judges.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,14,"PERSON"],[52,56,"PERSON"],[61,80,"PERSON"],[84,88,"PERSON"],[92,106,"GPE"],[178,183,"PERSON"]]}],["Viral mothers demanding alms in Sukabumi appeared in Cianjur. The latest news is that the woman also appeared in Bogor City.\r",{"entities":[[32,40,"PERSON"],[53,61,"GPE"],[113,123,"GPE"]]}],["The earthquake measuring M 6.2 which rocked the Garut Regency area had an impact as far away as Sumedang.\r",{"entities":[[48,61,"GPE"],[96,104,"GPE"]]}],["\"The M 6.2 earthquake in Garut, West Java caused a number of building damages, for example in Tasikmalaya there was damage to houses and schools.\"\r",{"entities":[[25,30,"GPE"],[32,41,"GPE"],[94,105,"GPE"]]}],["\"Two telecommunications company officers were found dead while checking the culverts on Jalan Sangkuriang, Bandung. The two of them were reportedly repairing the network at that location.\"\r",{"entities":[[88,105,"LOC"],[107,115,"GPE"]]}],["\"Four men in Banjar, South Kalimantan (Kalsel), were struck by lightning while fishing in a reservoir. The incident resulted in two people dying after falling into the reservoir.\"\r",{"entities":[[13,19,"GPE"],[21,37,"GPE"],[39,45,"GPE"]]}],["\"A shophouse in the Mustikajaya area, Bekasi City, West Java, experienced a fire. The Bekasi City Fire Department (Damkar) is already at the location to extinguish the fire.\"\r",{"entities":[[20,31,"LOC"],[38,49,"GPE"],[51,60,"GPE"]]}],["\"Polda Metro Jaya raided a synthetic tobacco home industry in the Sentul area, Bogor Regency, West Java. The perpetrators of this drug abuse case have also been arrested by the police.\"\r",{"entities":[[79,92,"GPE"],[94,104,"GPE"]]}],["\"Confession of co-worker Didi Hartanto, murder victim whose body was cast in Cimahi.\"\r",{"entities":[[25,38,"PERSON"],[77,83,"GPE"]]}],["\"\"\"Rob, rob, rob\"\" hoarse screams broke the quiet early morning in the residential area of ??Purbawinangun Village, Plumbon District, Cirebon Regency. The owner of the voice was identified as Edi, he was injured and died after being stabbed by an unknown person in the early hours of Tuesday (23/4).\"\r",{"entities":[[93,114,"LOC"],[116,132,"LOC"],[134,150,"GPE"],[192,195,"PERSON"]]}],["\"Police raided the Higgs Domino and Royal Dream online gambling headquarters in Depok, which had a turnover of up to IDR 30 billion. Four people were named as suspects in this online gambling case.\"\r",{"entities":[[80,85,"GPE"]]}],["\"84 residents experienced poisoning after eating a wedding celebration meal in Cisaah Village, Tugubandung Village, Kabandungan District, Sukabumi Regency on Sunday (28/4).\"\r",{"entities":[[79,93,"LOC"],[95,114,"LOC"],[116,136,"LOC"],[138,154,"GPE"]]}],["\"A tragic work accident occurred around the Sukajaya Village plantation, Urug Village, Kawalu District, Tasikmalaya City, Sunday (28/4) afternoon. A truck driver died allegedly due to a high voltage electric shock.\"\r",{"entities":[[44,60,"LOC"],[73,85,"LOC"],[87,102,"LOC"],[104,120,"GPE"]]}],["Farmers in Banjarnegara are screaming due to the drop in salak prices. Their harvest only sells for IDR 500 per kilogram.\r",{"entities":[[11,23,"GPE"]]}],["\"Braga Hotel parking attendant, Sokaraja District, Banyumas Regency, Fajar Subekti (38) was shot to death by a man. The shooter was immediately arrested. It turned out that the perpetrator was a guest who was reluctant to pay for parking.\"\r",{"entities":[[32,49,"LOC"],[51,67,"GPE"],[69,82,"PERSON"]]}],["\"Motorbike thieves were stripped naked and judged by the masses in Batang Regency, Central Java. This is what the police say.\"\r",{"entities":[[67,81,"GPE"],[83,96,"GPE"]]}],["\"A group of punk kids were arrested by the Jiken Police, Blora Regency. They were detained because they had blocked the truck by throwing stones.\"\r",{"entities":[[57,71,"GPE"]]}],["The people of Boyolali are asked to be alert again to cases of Foot and Mouth Disease (FMD). This is because diseases that attack cattle have been found again in a number of areas in Boyolali Regency.\r",{"entities":[[14,22,"GPE"],[183,199,"GPE"]]}],["\"Onion theft has recently become widespread in the onion center area in Brebes, Central Java. Generally, perpetrators target onions ready to be harvested or onions that are being dried in the sun after harvest.\"\r",{"entities":[[72,78,"GPE"],[80,93,"GPE"]]}],["\"A 4.9 magnitude tectonic earthquake rocked Cilacap, Central Java on Monday (22/4/2024). The vibrations were felt in several areas in West Java.\"\r",{"entities":[[44,51,"GPE"],[53,65,"GPE"],[134,143,"GPE"]]}],["\"Deputy Chief of Demak Police, Commissioner Aldino Agus Anggoro, said the three suspects had the initials DW (25), BB (24), MD (15). The three men are residents of Welahan District, Jepara. The victim was a man with the initials PAS (27), a resident of Mijen District, Demak.\"\r",{"entities":[[51,63,"PERSON"],[164,180,"LOC"],[182,189,"GPE"],[253,267,"LOC"],[269,274,"GPE"]]}],["\"Two children were swept away while fishing in the Glugu River, Grobogan Regency. One of the victims was found dead.\"\r",{"entities":[[51,62,"LOC"],[64,81,"GPE"]]}],["A young man in Jepara Regency was arrested by police after stabbing two people until one of them died. The stabbing occurred after the perpetrator and the victims fought at a female friend's boarding house.\r",{"entities":[[15,29,"GPE"]]}],["\"The woman with the initials S (22), a resident of Lemahbang Village, Jumapolo District, Karanganyar, was found dead wrapped in plastic and several personal items missing. The family said they had communicated with the victim via a messaging application.\"\r",{"entities":[[51,68,"LOC"],[70,87,"LOC"],[89,100,"GPE"]]}],["\"Recently, social media was shocked by the brave action of a pickup driver 'pushing back' two large buses going in the opposite direction in Kebumen, Central Java. He didn't let the bus pass by blocking the road!\"\r",{"entities":[[141,148,"GPE"],[150,163,"GPE"]]}],["\"Khoirul Anam (19) was arrested by the police for assaulting his employer, the owner of a cross-legged food stall in Kendal. He abused the victim using a hoe. The reason was that he did not accept being paid Rp. 70 thousand per day at the shop.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,13,"PERSON"],[117,124,"GPE"]]}],["\"Klaten cannot be separated from the nickname 'national food barn'. Under the leadership of Regent Sri Mulyani, a number of programs were launched to ensure agricultural productivity in Klaten continues to be maintained.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,7,"GPE"],[99,110,"PERSON"],[186,192,"GPE"]]}],["\"This angkringan is a hangout place for young people in Kudus Regency, Central Java, which is quite unique. Apart from offering the old Kudus atmosphere, this angkringan has a unique promotional style.\"\r",{"entities":[[56,69,"GPE"],[71,83,"GPE"]]}],["\"Grebeg Getuk The 1118th anniversary of Magelang City was very lively. Residents were very enthusiastic about welcoming the implementation of Grebeg Getuk, which had been on hiatus for 4 years.\"\r",{"entities":[[40,53,"GPE"]]}],["\"A woman with the initials SH (34), a resident of Pati District, Pati Regency, was arrested by traders and handed over to the police. SH is suspected of distributing counterfeit money to Kayen Market.\"\r",{"entities":[[50,63,"LOC"],[65,77,"GPE"],[187,199,"LOC"]]}],["\"A shortage of 3 kg subsidized LPG or Melon Gas occurred in Pekalongan, Central Java in the last week. This condition also caused prices to jump from IDR 20 thousand to IDR 40 thousand.\"\r",{"entities":[[60,70,"GPE"],[72,84,"GPE"]]}],["Minister of Agriculture (Mentan) Andi Amran Sulaiman was angry when he received a complaint from one of the farmers in Pemalang. The farmer complained that he had difficulty getting subsidized fertilizer.\r",{"entities":[[33,52,"PERSON"],[119,128,"GPE"]]}],["\"A man was arrested by the police after being caught by residents stealing the contents of the Baitu Salam Mosque charity box in Klapasawit Village, Kalimanah District, Purbalingga Regency.\"\r",{"entities":[[129,147,"LOC"],[149,167,"LOC"],[169,188,"GPE"]]}],["\"The Head of LKPP RI, Hendrar Prihadi or Hendi invited MSMEs in Purworejo to upgrade by participating in government procurement.\"\r",{"entities":[[22,37,"PERSON"],[41,46,"PERSON"],[64,73,"GPE"]]}],["\"A student with the initials R (15), a resident of Sendangmulyo Village, Kragan District, Rembang Regency, was found dead in a rice field.\"\r",{"entities":[[51,71,"LOC"],[73,88,"LOC"],[90,105,"GPE"]]}],["\"The people of Semarang City have recently been shocked by the circulation of a video of a raid on gambling activities at an elite house near Jatidiri Stadium, Semarang.\"\r",{"entities":[[15,28,"GPE"],[142,158,"LOC"],[160,168,"GPE"]]}],["PT Sari Warna Asli Textile Industry is a private company operating in the clothing industry.\r",{"entities":[[0,35,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT. Agung Sejahtera Sidoraharjatex has built trust by maintaining high factory efficiency, and product development by its human resources.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,35,"ORG"]]}],["\"Textile issuer PT Sri Rejeki Isman Tbk or Sritex is starting to sink into debt. In fact, Sritex is a company that has been around for more than 50 years and was successful because of the quality of its products.\"\r",{"entities":[[16,39,"ORG"],[43,49,"ORG"],[90,96,"ORG"]]}],["\"Established as a simple workshop, CV Karya Hidup Sentosa is growing rapidly in terms of business and human resources.\"\r",{"entities":[[35,57,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Steel Pipe Industry of Indonesia, Tbk. (PT SPINDO, Tbk.) is a steel pipe manufacturer with the largest production capacity in Indonesia and is experienced in producing various kinds of steel pipes/tubes and various other related products.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,42,"ORG"],[44,59,"ORG"]]}],["PT SMART Tbk (SMART) is one of the leading integrated and public palm oil-based consumer product companies in Indonesia that is committed to sustainable palm oil production.\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"ORG"],[14,19,"ORG"]]}],["PT Combiphar is a medicine manufacturing company from Indonesia which was founded in 1971 and currently produces and markets 200 brands of prescription and over-the-counter medicines.\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"ORG"],[54,63,"GPE"]]}],["PT International Chemical Industry or PT Intercallin is a company that produces electric batteries and flashlights under the ABC brand.\r",{"entities":[[0,34,"ORG"],[38,52,"ORG"]]}],["\"Shares of textile issuer PT Indo-Rama Synthetics Tbk (INDR) were sought after by investors when the price jumped to the all-time high closing level (ATH) of IDR 12,475/share in mid-June 2022.\"\r",{"entities":[[26,53,"ORG"]]}],["PT Indah Jaya Textile Industry was founded in 1962 to supply towels to the local market.\r",{"entities":[[0,30,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Eastern Pearl Flour Mills, located in Makassar, South Sulawesi, consists of 2 factories, namely one factory on the sea side and a second, newer factory on the city side, the two factories are connected by a sophisticated conveyor system.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,29,"ORG"],[42,50,"GPE"],[52,66,"GPE"]]}],["PT Indolakto is a company that produces types of drinks headquartered in Jakarta. PT Indolakto is one of the largest dairy product producing companies in Indonesia.\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"ORG"],[73,81,"GPE"],[82,94,"ORG"],[154,163,"GPE"]]}],["Inter World Steels Mills Indonesia was founded more than 50 years ago as the first company to produce strip plates in Indonesia.\r",{"entities":[[0,34,"ORG"],[118,127,"GPE"]]}],["PT. Mahkota Indonesia is engaged in chemical manufacturing.\r",{"entities":[[0,21,"ORG"]]}],["PT. Indofood Fortuna Makmur is a company that operates in the largest snack food production sector in Indonesia.\r",{"entities":[[0,27,"ORG"],[102,111,"GPE"]]}],["PT Hiba Utama is a group of companies engaged in transportation services since 1949.\r",{"entities":[[0,13,"ORG"]]}],["\"President Director and Chief Executive Officer of PT Indofood CBP Sukses Makmur Tbk (ICBP) Anthoni Salim, said that global economic challenges and the weakening of people's purchasing power are things that must be anticipated.\"\r",{"entities":[[51,84,"ORG"],[92,105,"PERSON"]]}],["\"PT Surya Rengo Containers (SRC), a related company conducting business in Indonesia, has opened a new factory in Karawang. This new factory is the fourth corrugated factory owned by SRC.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,26,"ORG"],[28,31,"ORG"],[75,84,"GPE"],[114,123,"GPE"],[183,186,"ORG"]]}],["PT Adira Dinamika Multi Finance Tbk (Adira Finance) is a well-known financing company in Indonesia which has been listed on the Indonesia Stock Exchange (BEI) since 2004 as a company in the financial services sector with the trading code ADMF.\r",{"entities":[[0,35,"ORG"],[37,50,"ORG"],[89,98,"GPE"]]}],["\"PT Caturkarsa Megatunggal as controlling shareholder of PT Lautan Luas Tbk. (LTLS) has increased its share ownership portion on July 8, 2022.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,26,"ORG"],[57,76,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Caturkarsa Megatunggal as controlling shareholder of PT Lautan Luas Tbk. (LTLS) has increased its share ownership portion on July 8, 2022.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,26,"ORG"],[57,76,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Tri Sapta Jaya has become a part of supporting the health of the Indonesian people through the distribution of quality medicines throughout Indonesia, even in small towns.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,18,"ORG"]]}],["\"Forty years ago the Prasetiya Mulya foundation was born, on May 19 1980 to be precise.\"\r",{"entities":[[21,47,"ORG"]]}],["PT Enseval Putera Megatrading Tbk's fifty years of work with sustainable growth is proof of Enseval's dedication to dynamic and responsive innovation to provide reliable service to all customers.\r",{"entities":[[0,33,"ORG"]]}],["PT Bintang Toedjoe is a consumer health company which is a subsidiary of the Kalbe Group.\r",{"entities":[[0,18,"ORG"],[77,88,"ORG"]]}],["PT Astra Otoparts Tbk (AUTO) concluded its General Shareholders Meeting (GMS) on Friday (26/4) to discuss the financial report for the 2023 financial year.\r",{"entities":[[0,21,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Menjangan Sakti focuses on several innovative businesses, such as pharmaceuticals, foodstuffs, animal feed, cosmetics, biotechnology and health equipment.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,19,"ORG"]]}],["\"Founded in 2000, PT Tigaka Distrindo Perkasa (TDP) is a company within Anugerah Corporation, an Indonesian group that focuses on health and fitness services.\"\r",{"entities":[[18,45,"ORG"],[72,92,"ORG"]]}],["\"The subsidiary of the coal mining company PT Indo Tambangraya Megah Tbk (ITMG), namely PT Trubaindo Coal Mining (PT TCM), was questioned by Commission VII DPR, Wednesday (05/07/2023).\"\r",{"entities":[[43,72,"ORG"],[88,112,"ORG"],[114,120,"ORG"]]}],["PT ALTRAK 1978 is one of the well-established companies operating as a Sole Agent and Distributor of Heavy Equipment in Indonesia.\r",{"entities":[[0,14,"ORG"],[120,129,"GPE"]]}],["\"PT. Unggul Indah Cahaya Tbk is the sole producer of Alkylbenzene (AB), one of the main raw materials for detergents.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,28,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Indominco Mandiri (IMM) is a subsidiary of PT Indo Tambangraya Megah Tbk (ITM) whose business fields are mining, construction and general trading.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,21,"ORG"],[47,76,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Indomobil Finance Indonesia is a company engaged in the business of financing motorbikes, cars, commercial vehicles, heavy equipment, machinery, property, multipurpose and micro business financing as well as sharia financing which was founded on November 1 1993.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,31,"ORG"]]}],["PT. Inti Everspring Indonesia is looking for individuals who have the potential and competence who can improve the quality of production and development of a company that has been operating in the chemical sector since 1992.\r",{"entities":[[0,29,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Ina Sekuritas Indonesia (formerly Nikko Sekuritas Indonesia) is a securities company headquartered in Jakarta, Indonesia and founded in 1990.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,27,"ORG"],[38,63,"ORG"]]}],["North Penajam Paser Regency DPRD (PPU) is encouraging the resolution of the PT Kebun Mandiri Sejahtera (KMS) polemic with residents around the plantation area.\r",{"entities":[[76,102,"ORG"]]}],["\"Founded in 1991, PT Rintis Sejahtera (RINTIS) is a company engaged in the operation of VSAT satellite communication systems.\"\r",{"entities":[[18,37,"ORG"]]}],["PT Mitrausaha Gentaniaga (Honda Mugen) is an official Honda dealer located in West Jakarta and South Jakarta.\r",{"entities":[[0,24,"ORG"],[78,90,"GPE"],[95,108,"GPE"]]}],["PT AKR Corporindo Tbk currently has more than 130 SPBN and SPBKB distribution networks spread across 65 regencies/cities in 11 provinces throughout Indonesia.\r",{"entities":[[0,21,"ORG"]]}],["PT. Inbisco Niagatama Semesta is a distributor that specializes in distributing products from the Mayora Group which has 8 branch offices.\r",{"entities":[[0,29,"ORG"],[98,110,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Total Bangun Persada Tbk is a building construction company headquartered in Jakarta, Indonesia.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,28,"ORG"],[81,88,"GPE"],[90,99,"GPE"]]}],["\"PT Indofood Sukses Makmur Tbk (INDF) or better known as Indofood is a producer of various types of food and beverages headquartered in Jakarta, Indonesia.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,30,"ORG"],[136,143,"GPE"],[145,154,"GPE"]]}],["PT Kalbe Farma Tbk is a pharmaceutical company headquartered in Jakarta. This company's products are sold in 43 countries spread across 5 continents.\r",{"entities":[[0,18,"ORG"],[64,72,"GPE"]]}],["\"PT Djembatan Dua is trusted by its business partners who are leading multi-national companies in its segments from Asia, America and Europe.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,17,"ORG"],[116,120,"GPE"],[122,129,"GPE"],[134,140,"GPE"]]}],["PT Indomarco Prismatama (Indomaret Group) is a subsidiary of the Salim Group which was founded in 1988.\r",{"entities":[[0,23,"ORG"],[25,40,"ORG"],[65,76,"ORG"]]}],["PT Summarecon Agung Tbk is a property company headquartered in Jakarta.\r",{"entities":[[0,23,"ORG"],[63,70,"GPE"]]}],["\"Founded in 1990 and commercially operated in August 1993, PT Sanpak Unggul produces plastic packaging for personal care, household, food, lubricants, chemical, pharmaceutical industries, promotional items and automotive/engineering components.\"\r",{"entities":[[59,75,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT. Srikandi Diamond Motors is a company operating in the automotive sector, specifically in selling cars along with service and maintenance.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,28,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Muliaglass operates in the glass industry with sheet glass, glass blocks, glass packaging and automotive safety glass as its production products.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,14,"ORG"]]}],["PT Indocement Tunggal Prakarsa Tbk (INTP) is one of the cement producers in Indonesia. Indocement is the second largest producer in Indonesia.\r",{"entities":[[0,34,"ORG"],[132,141,"GPE"]]}],["PT Kitadin is a leading coal mining company in Indonesia and is part of the Indo Tambangraya Megah business group.\r",{"entities":[[0,10,"ORG"],[47,56,"GPE"],[76,98,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Indah Kiat Pulp & Paper Tbk is a pulp, paper and tissue manufacturer headquartered in Jakarta.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,31,"ORG"],[90,97,"GPE"]]}],["\"Founded in 1957, PT Meratus Line was the first Indonesian shipping company to operate dedicated container liner services in 1990.\"\r",{"entities":[[18,33,"ORG"]]}],["PT Indopoly Swakarsa Industry Tbk is a public company in Indonesia (IPOL) which is engaged in the business of manufacturing plastic products intended for the flexible packaging industry.\r",{"entities":[[0,33,"ORG"],[57,66,"GPE"]]}],["\"PT Japfa Comfeed Indonesia, Tbk is one of the largest and leading agri-food companies in the country.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,32,"ORG"]]}],["\"The Business Competition Supervisory Commission (KPPU) imposed a fine on PT. Hok Tong amounted to IDR 2 billion for late notification of acquisition transactions carried out for three companies, namely PT Pulau Bintan Djaya, PT Sumber Djantin, and PT Sumber Alam.\"\r",{"entities":[[74,86,"ORG"],[203,224,"ORG"],[226,243,"ORG"],[249,263,"ORG"]]}],["PT Indomarco Adi Prima is a company engaged in the distributor and importer of consumer goods.\r",{"entities":[[0,22,"ORG"]]}],["\"Dexa Medica, one of Indonesia's largest pharmaceutical companies, has consistently used its advanced research capabilities to prioritize the health needs of the Indonesian people.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,12,"ORG"],[21,30,"GPE"]]}],["PT. Dunia Kimia Utama is the first and only industry in South Sumatra to produce sulfuric acid and aluminum sulfate.\r",{"entities":[[0,21,"ORG"],[56,69,"GPE"]]}],["PT ORIX Indonesia Finance (ORIF) was established as a joint venture between ORIX Corporation (85%) and the Bank Indonesia Employee Welfare Foundation (15%).\r",{"entities":[[0,25,"ORG"],[76,92,"ORG"],[107,149,"ORG"]]}],["PT. Remco is an agro-industrial company that operates in the field of processing rubber from processed rubber (bokar) in the form of slabs and lumps to produce crumb rubber of the Standard Indonesian Rubber (SIR) type.\r",{"entities":[[0,9,"ORG"]]}],["PT Sinar Alam Permai is a Foreign Capital Company (PMA) which operates in the field of palm oil processing.\r",{"entities":[[0,20,"ORG"]]}],["PT Ultrajaya Milk Industry & Trading Company Tbk is a beverage manufacturer headquartered in West Bandung.\r",{"entities":[[0,48,"ORG"],[93,105,"GPE"]]}],["\"For more than 4 decades, PT Anugrah Argon Medica (AAM) has developed end-to-end competency which provides significant added value in terms of service to customers and business partners.\"\r",{"entities":[[26,49,"ORG"]]}],["PT Soho Industri Pharmasi won 3rd place (Gold) in the BPOM Award for Environmental Sustainability in the 2023 Pharmaceutical & Food Industry.\r",{"entities":[[0,25,"ORG"]]}],["PT Nojorono Tobacco International is one of the pioneer companies in kretek cigarettes in Indonesia.\r",{"entities":[[0,33,"ORG"],[90,99,"GPE"]]}],["CV. Surya Indah Motor Jepara is a company that operates in the automotive sector.\r",{"entities":[[0,28,"ORG"]]}],["PT Mandalatama Armada Motor celebrates its 34th anniversary on August 3 2021.\r",{"entities":[[0,27,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT. Hexpharm Jaya Laboratories, which was founded in 1971, is specifically engaged in the development, production and marketing of medicines.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,31,"ORG"]]}],["PT. Catur Adiluhur Sentosa Jambi is a company engaged in trading industrial goods.\r",{"entities":[[0,26,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT. Duta Putera Sumatra, is an ATPM (Sole Brand Holder Agent) of the MAN Truck brand truck unit.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,24,"ORG"]]}],["PT Ciliandra Perkasa builds sustainable palm oil production for the progress of Indonesia.\r",{"entities":[[0,20,"ORG"],[80,89,"GPE"]]}],["\"PT. Arindo Trisejahtera is located at Jl. Sudirman Pekanbaru, operates in the palm oil plantation business.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,24,"ORG"],[39,51,"LOC"],[52,61,"GPE"]]}],["PT. Meridan Sejatisurya Plantation operates in the oil palm plantation sector with an integrated processing unit that produces palm oil and palm kernel.\r",{"entities":[[0,34,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Bumen Redja Abadi is an Official Mitsubishi Motors and Fuso Dealer that provides sales, maintenance, body repairs and original Mitsubishi spare parts.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,21,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Multi Garmenjaya is a manufacturing company that produces various types of clothing and other accessories such as t-shirts, shirts, suits, jackets, trousers, belts, hats, bags and shoes.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,20,"ORG"]]}],["PT Daliatex Kusuma is collaborating again with local brands to support the program of the Ministry of Trade of the Republic of Indonesia which wants to develop the Indonesian fashion industry.\r",{"entities":[[0,18,"ORG"]]}],["PT Plumbon International Textile is a company that has the legal entity form of a limited liability company.\r",{"entities":[[0,32,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Sanghiang Perkasa or known as KALBE Nutritionals is part of PT KALBE Farma Tbk. which is one of the leading pharmaceutical companies from Indonesia, and is well known on a national and international scale.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,21,"ORG"],[34,52,"ORG"],[64,83,"ORG"],[142,151,"GPE"]]}],["\"Currently, PT. Sinar Mas Insurance is one of the largest insurance companies in Indonesia.\"\r",{"entities":[[12,35,"ORG"],[81,90,"GPE"]]}],["\"PT Timah Tbk is part of MIND ID which is mainly engaged in tin, coal and nickel mining.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,13,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT TIMAH is a producer and exporter of tin metal, and has an integrated tin mining business segment starting from exploration, mining, processing to marketing activities.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,9,"ORG"]]}],["PT. Indonesian Acids Industry was founded in 1969 to produce sulfuric acid and aluminum sulfate.\r",{"entities":[[0,29,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Metropolitan Kentjana Tbk is a property company headquartered in Pondok Indah, Jakarta and controlled by the Central Cipta Murdaya group (formerly the Salim Group until 2002).\"\r",{"entities":[[1,29,"ORG"],[69,81,"LOC"],[83,90,"GPE"],[113,140,"ORG"],[155,166,"ORG"]]}],["PT Nirwana Lestari is a subsidiary of the Delfi Limited Group which was founded as a marketing and distribution company for Delfi products since 1986.\r",{"entities":[[0,18,"ORG"],[42,61,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT. Prima Jaya Perkasa is engaged in the transportation sector, this company has made a lot of progress and now to be more trusted by the public, we always try our best in providing services to our partners.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,23,"ORG"]]}],["\"Since 1971, PT Bernofarm has grown into a widely known name in the pharmaceutical business.\"\r",{"entities":[[13,25,"ORG"]]}],["PT Federal International Finance (FIFGROUP) is a company founded in Indonesia under the name PT Mitrapusaka Artha Finance in May 1989 by Astra which provides conventional and sharia financing facilities.\r",{"entities":[[0,32,"ORG"],[93,121,"ORG"]]}],["PT Serasi Autoraya (SERA) is a subsidiary of PT Astra International Tbk which is now widely known as one of the largest transportation and logistics service companies in Indonesia.\r",{"entities":[[0,18,"ORG"],[45,71,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Bumi Pratama Khatulistiwa (BPK) security officers succeeded in arresting two residents of Kubu Raya Regency who were caught stealing palm fruit, at the location of Sungai Malaya Village, Sungai Ambawang District, Kubu Raya Regency, on Saturday (16/12/2023), at around 04.00 Wib.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,29,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT XL Axiata Tbk (EXCL, previously known as PT Excelcomindo Pratama Tbk) or abbreviated as XL is a cellular telecommunications operator company in Indonesia.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,17,"ORG"],[45,72,"ORG"]]}],["PT JACCS Mitra Pinasthika Mustika Finance Indonesia posted a decline in net profit throughout last year.\r",{"entities":[[0,51,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Panin Sekuritas is one of the leading securities companies that exists to answer the investment needs of investors, both individuals, private companies and government institutions.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,19,"ORG"]]}],["PT Bangunreksa Perkasa is a granite distributor company.\r",{"entities":[[0,22,"ORG"]]}],["PT Danareksa (Persero) is an Indonesian state-owned company that operates across sectors (conglomerate).\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"ORG"]]}],["\"BPK Penabur Foundation, an institution operating in the field of education, is looking for young professionals who have interest, integrity and a high desire to progress and develop with us.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,23,"ORG"]]}],["PT Freyabadi Indotama was founded in 1995 through collaboration between Fuji Oil Holdings Japan and McKeeson Investments from Singapore.\r",{"entities":[[0,21,"ORG"],[72,95,"ORG"],[100,120,"ORG"],[126,135,"GPE"]]}],["PT Samuel Sekuritas Indonesia (SSI) is a member of the Indonesian Stock Exchange and has a license as a Securities Broker and Underwriter.\r",{"entities":[[0,29,"ORG"]]}],["\"Depo Gedung is a pioneer that introduced a way of shopping for building materials with the One-Stop Shopping concept in Indonesia, with a legal entity founded in 1996 called PT Caturkarda Depo Bangunan, Tbk.\"\r",{"entities":[[175,207,"ORG"]]}],["PT Sumber Alfaria Trijaya Tbk (doing business under the name Alfamart) is a retail trading company headquartered in Tangerang.\r",{"entities":[[0,29,"ORG"],[61,69,"ORG"],[116,125,"GPE"]]}],["\"PT Astra Sedaya Finance (usually abbreviated as ASF) is a financing company that is wholly owned by PT Astra International, Tbk.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,24,"ORG"],[101,128,"ORG"]]}],["PT. SO GOOD FOOD is part of JAPFA which operates in the food processing industry\r",{"entities":[[0,16,"ORG"]]}],["PT. Nusantara Surya Sakti is the company that the author chose as a research location that raises issues regarding employee performance.\r",{"entities":[[0,25,"ORG"]]}],["PT. Indokemika Jayatama operates in the integrated chemical trading business.\r",{"entities":[[0,23,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Telekomunikasi Selular or commonly abbreviated as Telkomsel, is a subsidiary of Telkom Indonesia which operates in the telecommunications sector for individual consumers (until 2023 it only deals in cellular telecommunications).\"\r",{"entities":[[1,26,"ORG"],[54,63,"ORG"],[84,100,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Perusahaan Industri Ceres (Delfi Group) is a private company that produces chocolate-based foods under the Delfi, Chunky Bar, Top and Ceres brands.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,29,"ORG"],[31,42,"ORG"]]}],["\"The owner and Finance Director of PT The Master Steel Manufactory, Diah Soemedi, was sentenced to 5 years in prison, plus a fine of IDR 100 million, subsidiary to 3 months in prison in the tax officer bribery case.\"\r",{"entities":[[35,66,"ORG"]]}],["PT. Ecogreen Oleochemicals is one of the world's leading producers of Natural Fatty Alcohol.\r",{"entities":[[0,26,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Cyberindo Aditama is a company operating in the technology, information and communications sector in Indonesia which provides various products such as internet services, data centers, Cloud Computing and Interactive TV.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,21,"ORG"]]}],["PT Clipan Finance Indonesia Tbk (abbreviated as ClipanFinance) is a public financing company in Indonesia (CFIN).\r",{"entities":[[0,31,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Triwarga Dian Sakti has employees, where every month they will receive a salary that must be paid to employees because of their work at a company.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,23,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT BNI Sekuritas is a leading, trusted and innovative company that provides financial solutions services in the Indonesian capital markets industry with the support of superior quality human resources and leading technology.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,17,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT ETHICA Industri Farmasi is the first pharmaceutical company in Indonesia to have sterile technology with the most advanced facilities with an area of ??more than 52,000 m2.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,27,"ORG"]]}],["\"\"\"We have sent a summons to the company, and asked the chicken farming company PT Leong Ayam Satu Primadona to attend this Friday,\"\" said Artini Marpaung, head of the Deli Serdang environmental service to media journalists when confirmed via cellphone Wednesday (29/6/2022 ).\"\r",{"entities":[[80,108,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT INDONESIA LIBOLON FIBER SYSTEM is a textile manufacturing company that has expertise in the production and development of various types of textile products located in Purwakarta, West Java.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,34,"ORG"],[171,181,"GPE"],[183,192,"GPE"]]}],["PT Dharma Satya Nusantara Tbk (doing business under the name DSN Group) is an agro-industrial company headquartered in Jakarta.\r",{"entities":[[0,29,"ORG"],[119,126,"GPE"]]}],["PT Lajuperdana Indah is a sugar factory company.\r",{"entities":[[0,20,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Dynaplast operates in the plastic industry,\"\r",{"entities":[[1,13,"ORG"]]}],["\"As a leading motorbike and car financing company in Indonesia, PT Wahana Ottomitra Multiartha, Tbk (WOM Finance) has quite a long history.\"\r",{"entities":[[64,99,"ORG"],[101,112,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT Olam Indonesia is the largest exporter of Robusta coffee, Arabica and leading cocoa products in Indonesia with a combined market share of around 15%.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,18,"ORG"]]}],["\"PT. Tri Keeson Utama Garut is a company engaged in the production of cocoa powder blending/mixing, namely producing semi-finished chocolate powder which is intended for other chocolate processing industries throughout Indonesia.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,21,"ORG"],[219,228,"GPE"]]}],["PT Inti Ganda Perdana is part of the IGP Group which is a group of companies operating in the automotive components sector.\r",{"entities":[[0,21,"ORG"],[37,46,"ORG"]]}],["\"As a result of PT Hijau Pertiwi Indah Plantations (HPIP) not providing severance pay to elderly workers, the workers filed a lawsuit at the Kuala Kapuas District Court, this was confirmed by the Plaintiffs' Attorney M. Junaedi L Gaol, SH.\"\r",{"entities":[[16,50,"ORG"],[52,56,"ORG"]]}],["PT. Srikandi Diamond Motors is only a company operating in the automotive sector.\r",{"entities":[[0,27,"ORG"]]}],["",{"entities":[]}]]}